[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":141929,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":2701648,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure  that whe n we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":9321,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":2710979,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"4 + 5 = 9","response_history":["4 = ","4 =","4 + 5 = 9"],"rt":10888,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":2721870,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2866,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":2724738,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":10247,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":2734987,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1389,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":2736379,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result . If the  sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":7950,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":2744331,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":3382,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":2747715,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4342,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":2752059,"internal_chunk_id":"0- 0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1263,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":2753323,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2967,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":2756291,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":4501,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":2760794,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br />< br /> (R emember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":7336,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":2768131,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1654,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":2769787,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4 ","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3406,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":2773195,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":2150,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":2775347,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3479,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":2778827,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1837,"trial_type":"feed back","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":2780666,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3144,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":2783811,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1542,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":2785355,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum  is smal ler than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3142,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":2788499,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1604,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":2790107,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":34228,"trial_type":"ins truction s","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":2824340,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":46847,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":2871188,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":15886,"trial_type":" question ","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":2887076,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1238,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":2888316,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4758,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":2893076,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1127,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":2894205,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2173,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":2896380,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":982,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":2897364,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2551,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":2899916,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1126,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":2901044,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2223,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":2903268,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3886,"trial_type":"fee dback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":2907156,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":15014,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":2922172,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element  under +< sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":27998,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":2950172,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":32310,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":2982485,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":2323,"trial_type":"f eedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":2984812,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":4288,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":2989101,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":1740,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":2990844,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":81014,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":3071861,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1686,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":3073549,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No ","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":2710,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":3076262,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1934,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":3078197,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice questi on with  feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":7766,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":3085965,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3709,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":3089677,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1056,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":3090734,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3278,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":3094013,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2639,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":3096653,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2790,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":3099445,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2288,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":3101735,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":" 3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2629,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":3104366,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":7276,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":3111643,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3. 8 + 4 = 12. Since it is more than 9, I subtract 9 .  12-9 = 3","response_history":["3. 8 =","3. 8 + 4 +","3. 8 + 4 = 12. Since it is more than 9, i ","3. 8 + 4 = 12. Since it is more than 9, i","3. 8 + 4 = 12. Since it is more than 9, I subra","3. 8 + 4 = 12. Since it is more than 9, I subr","3. 8 + 4 = 12. Since it is more than 9,  I subtra ct 9 from ","3. 8 + 4 = 12. Since it is more than 9, I subtract 9 from the ","3. 8 + 4 = 12. Since it is more than 9, I subtract 9 from the","3. 8 + 4 = 12. Since it is more than 9, I subtract 9 from th","3. 8 + 4 = 12. Since it is more than 9, I subtract 9 from t","3. 8 + 4 = 12. Since it is more than 9, I subtract 9 from ","3. 8 + 4 = 12. Since it is more than 9, I subtract 9 from","3. 8 + 4 = 12. Since it is more than 9, I subtract 9 fro","3. 8 + 4 = 12. Since it is more than 9, I subtract 9 fr","3. 8 + 4 = 12. Since it is more than 9, I subtract 9 f","3. 8 + 4 = 12. Since it is more than 9, I subtract 9 .  12-9 +","3. 8 + 4 = 12. Since it is more than 9, I subtract 9 .  12-9 = 3"],"rt":45953,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":3157598,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0. Because when I combine it wih 9, i get 9 as the result","response_history":["0. Because when I combine it wih 9, i","0. Because when I combine it wih 9, i get 9 as the result"],"rt":71774,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":3229375,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["5","4"],"rt":41486,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":3270863,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":479983,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":3750849,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","response_history":["9"],"rt":3363,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":3754215,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"The inverse is the number that you use to get the identity. So, the inverse must be 9 because 3+9-9=3","response_history":["he","h","Teh","Te","The inverse is the number that you use to get the identity. so","The inverse is the number that you use to get the identity. s","The inverse is the number that you use to get the identity. So, the inverse must be 9 beuc","The inverse is the number that you use to get the identity. So, the inverse must be 9 beu","The inverse is the number that you use to get the identity. So, the inverse must be 9 because 3=","The inverse is the nu mber tha t you use to get the identity. So, the inverse must be 9 because 3+9-9+","The inverse is the number that you use to get the identity. So, the inverse must be 9 because 3+9-9+","The inverse is the number that you use to get the identity. So, the inverse must be 9 because 3+9-9=3"],"rt":89641,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":3843857,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No.You can't use 2 to make 3, 5, or 7 under 9","response_history":["No.You can't use 2 to make 3, 5, or 7 under 9"],"rt":58094,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":3901953,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No. YOu can't use 3 to make all of the other numbers under 9. ","response_history":["No ","No. YOu can't use 3 to make al ","No. YOu can't use 3 to make all of the other numbers under 9. "],"rt":56207,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":3958162,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes. 5 will work to give you all of the other numbers under 9.  ","response_history":["No. Y","No. ","No.","No","N","Ys","Yes. 5 will wr","Yes. 5 will wro","Yes. 5 will wr","Yes. 5 will wrok","Yes. 5 will wro","Yes. 5 will wr","Yes. 5 will work to give you all of the other numbers under 9.  For instance","Yes. 5 will work to give you all of the other numbers under 9.  For instanc","Yes. 5 will work to give you all of the other numbers under 9.  "],"rt":58079,"trial_type":" question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":4016243,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No. 6 will not work to give you 1 or 2 under 9","response_history":["No. 6 will not work to give you 1 or 3","No. 6 will not work to give you 1 or 2 under 9"],"rt":24460,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":4040706,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":8359,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":4049067,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":" n+1 _n=0","response_history":[" ="," _"," ="," + _n=0"," +1 _n=0"," n+1 _n=0"],"rt":99015,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":4148084,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x + _n = 0   I don't know how to solve this if I don't know the value of x or _n","response_history":["x =","x + _n +","x + _n = 0  X must be -n","x + _n = 0  X","x + _n = 0   I dont ","x + _n = 0   I dont","x + _n = 0   I don't know how to solve this if I don't know the value of x or _n"],"rt":52675,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":4200764,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I am not sure if there is a pattern.  I understood this lesson when there were numbers given to solve or write equations. But, I have no idea how to even guess at what might be generators for unknown numbers","response_history":["I am not sure if there is a pattern.  I don't know how to solve ","I am not sure if there is a pattern.  I understool","I am not sure if there is a pattern.  I understood this lesson when there were numbers igv","I am not sure if there is a pattern.  I understood this lesson when there were numbers ig","I am not sure if there is a pattern.  I understood this lesson when there were numbers i","I am not sure if there is a patt ern.  I  understood this lesson when there were numbers given to solve or wrie e","I am not sure if there is a pattern.  I understood this lesson when there were numbers given to solve or wrie ","I am not sure if there is a pattern.  I understood this lesson when there were numbers given to solve or wrie","I am not sure if there is a pattern.  I understood this lesson when there were numbers given to solve or write q","I am not sure if there is a pattern.  I understood this lesson when there were numbers given to solve or write equations. b","I am not sure if there is a pattern.  I understood this lesson when there were numbers given to solve or write equations. Bu,t ","I am not sure if there is a pattern.  I understood this lesson when there were numbers given to solve or write equations. Bu,t","I am not sure if there is a pattern.  I understood this lesson when there were numbers given to solve or write equations. Bu,","I am not sure if there is a pattern.  I understood this lesson  when th ere were numbers given to solve or write equations. But, I have no idea how to even guess at which ","I am not sure if there is a pattern.  I understood this lesson when there were numbers given to solve or write equations. But, I have no idea how to even guess at which","I am not sure if there is a pattern.  I understood this lesson when there were numbers given to solve or write equations. But, I have no idea how to even guess at whic","I am not sure if there is a pattern.  I understood this lesson when there were numbers given to solve or write equations. But, I have no idea how to even guess at whi","I am not sure if there is a pattern.  I understood this lesson when there were numbers given to solve or write equations. But, I have no idea how to even guess at what might be generators for unknown numbers"],"rt":85158,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":4285925,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is a n odd nu mber, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":15046,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":4300973,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["True","False"],"rt":6621,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":4307597,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":23750,"trial_type":"q uestion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":4331350,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"I think this is true because we must always end with a whole number when solving these equations.","response_history":["I think this is true w","I think this is true because we musta","I think this is true because we must alwasy e","I think this is true because we must alwasy ","I think this is true because we must alwasy","I think this is true because we must alwas","I think this is true because we must alwaye","I think this is true because we must always i","I think this is true because we must always end iwth a","I think this is true because we must always end iwth ","I think this is true because we must always end iwth","I t hink thi s is true because we must always end iwt","I think this is true because we must always end iw","I think this is true because we must always end i","I think this is true because we must always end with a whol nu","I think this is true because we must always end with a whol n","I think this is true because we must always end with a whol ","I think this is true because we must always end with a whole number when solving these equations."],"rt":49166,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":4380518,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":18747,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":4399270,"internal_chunk_id":" 0-0.14-0 "},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"I have no idea. I'm going to guess sometimes. I don't understand how to determine this when I don't have any actual values for the numbers","response_history":["I have no diea.","I have no diea","I have no die","I have no di","I have no d","I have no idea. I'm going go","I have no idea. I'm going g","I have no idea. I'm going t o","I have no idea. I'm going t ","I have no idea. I'm going to guess sometimes. I","I have no idea. I'm going to guess sometimes. But, I think that ","I have no idea. I'm going to guess sometimes. I dont' unde","I have no idea. I'm going to guess sometimes. I dont' und","I have no idea. I'm going to guess sometimes. I dont' un","I have no idea. I'm going to guess s ometimes . I dont' u","I have no idea. I'm going to guess sometimes. I dont' ","I have no idea. I'm going to guess sometimes. I dont'","I have no idea. I'm going to guess sometimes. I dont","I have no idea. I'm going to guess sometimes. I don","I have no idea. I'm going to guess sometimes. I don't su","I have no idea. I'm going to guess sometimes. I don't s","I have no idea. I'm going to guess sometimes. I don't undersa","I have no idea. I'm going to guess sometimes. I don't understand ho t","I have no idea. I'm going to guess sometimes. I don't understand ho ","I have no idea. I'm going to guess sometimes. I don't understand how to determine this when I don't have any actual values for the numbers"],"rt":62118,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":4461390,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":14510,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":4475903,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":2269,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":4478174,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"41","response_history":["41"],"rt":2918,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":4481094,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Ba chelors  Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":4030,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":4485127,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Algebra 3/4 in high school.  College Math (for non-science majors)","response_history":["Algebra 3/4 in high school.  One cl","Algebra 3/4 in high school.  One college math ","Algebra 3/4 in high school.  One c","Algebra 3/4 in high school.  One ","Algebra 3/4 in high school.  One","Algebra 3/4 in high school.  On","Algebra 3/4 in high school.  O","Algebra 3/4 in high school.  College Math (for liber","Algebra 3/4 in high s chool.   College Math (for libe","Algebra 3/4 in high school.  College Math (for lib","Algebra 3/4 in high school.  College Math (for li","Algebra 3/4 in high school.  College Math (for l","Algebra 3/4 in high school.  College Math (for non-science majors)"],"rt":47454,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":4532583,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":6998,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":4539583,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":" How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":4756,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":4544343,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2814,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":4547159,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the conce pts in t his HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4902,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":4552063,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":2429,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":4554495,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":2045,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":4556543,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Wha t is/are  your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"english","response_history":["english"],"rt":6909,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":4563455,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I took notes on the definitions (inverse, identity, etc)","response_history":["I took notes onteh ","I took notes onteh","I took notes onte","I took notes ont ","I took notes ont","I took notes on the definitions (inverse, identity, etc)"],"rt":29917,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":4593375,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"This  was int eresting and (mostly) enjoyable. I really did not understand that last part of it, though.","response_history":["This was interesting and (mostly) n","This was interesting and (mostly) enjoyable. I really didn","This was interesting and (mostly) enjoyable. I really did not understand that last part of t","This was interesting and (mostly) enjoyable. I really did not understand that last part of it, when","This was interesting and (mostly) enjoyable. I really did not understand that last part of it, whe","This was interesting and (mostly) enjoyable. I really did not understand that last part of it, wh","This was interesting and (mostly) enjoyable. I really did not understand that last part of it, w","This was interesting and (mostly) enjoyable. I really did not understand that last part of it, ","This was interesting and (mostly) enjoyable. I really did not understand that last part of it,","This was interesting and (mostly) enjoyable. I really did not understand that last pa rt of it , though."],"rt":27231,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":4620609,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]